{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes","type":"FeatureCollection","@context":"https://w3id.org/locolligo/contexts/linkedplaces.jsonld","features":[{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/f7a4f5a9-f689-4c64-8d14-236b6599ba06","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"MCT 044, YBC 07302 P255051","dominant_interest":"Cuneiform Tablet","source_mentioned_in":"MCT 044, YBC 07302 P255051","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"1900 BC","end_date":"1600 BC","interesrt":"Geometry, Arithmetic","start":-1900,"end":-1600,"median":-1750,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":null},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/e0a0d2c7-4a57-4abf-b251-8f1adfabd8d9","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"MCT 057 (P255065) ","dominant_interest":"Cuneiform Tablet","source_mentioned_in":"MCT 057 (P255065) ","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"1900 BC","end_date":"1600 BC","location":"Uruk","place_type":"urban area, settlement","interesrt":"Geometry, Arithmetic","start":-1900,"end":-1600,"median":-1750,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[45.638327,31.3216128]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/46e9950c-65f2-4873-b342-55219552904a","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"TMS p.025 P254835","dominant_interest":"Cuneiform Tablet","source_mentioned_in":"TMS p.025 P254835","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"1900 BC","end_date":"1600 BC","location":"Susa","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Geometry, Arithmetic","start":-1900,"end":-1600,"median":-1750,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[48.2537285,32.1887935]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/742eb77c-e766-420d-b680-35258407b9ce","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Kahun Papyrus IV. 3 Cols. 15-14","dominant_interest":"Papyri","source_mentioned_in":"Kahun Papyrus","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"1896 BC","end_date":"1802 BC","location":"El Lahun","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Geometry, Arithmetic","start":-1896,"end":-1802,"median":-1849,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[30.8399565,29.3149635]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/d7449e57-9675-405b-89c4-178aeed859f5","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Problem 41","dominant_interest":"Papyri","source_mentioned_in":"Rhind Papyrys","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"1844 BC","end_date":"1797 BC","location":"Faiyum","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Geometry, Arithmetic","profession":"Scribe (Ahmes)","start":-1844,"end":-1797,"median":-1821,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[30.8399565,29.3149635]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/5160d141-8571-49d6-b18a-c277eef4e7e2","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Problem 43","dominant_interest":"Papyri","source_mentioned_in":"Rhind Papyrys","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"1844 BC","end_date":"1797 BC","location":"Faiyum","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Geometry, Arithmetic","profession":"Scribe (Ahmes)","start":-1844,"end":-1797,"median":-1821,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[30.8399565,29.3149635]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/c45e87f1-37e9-4428-843e-982c9759ee8c","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Problem 10","dominant_interest":"Papyri","source_mentioned_in":"Moscow Papyrys","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"1803 BC","end_date":"1649 BC","location":"Faiyum","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Geometry, Arithmetic","start":-1803,"end":-1649,"median":-1726,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[30.8399565,29.3149635]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/d3158c02-c675-4226-a545-4b2e2b18541d","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"1 Kings 7:23","dominant_interest":"Bible","source_mentioned_in":"Bible","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"0700 BC","end_date":"0600 BC","location":"Jerusalem","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Theology","profession":"Phrophet / Scribe (Jeremiah)","start":-700,"end":-600,"median":-650,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[35.234156,31.776679]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/19183770-2038-4adc-9516-ff7729797979","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"2 Chronicles 4:2","dominant_interest":"Bible","source_mentioned_in":"Bible","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"0500 BC","end_date":"0400 BC","location":"Jerusalem","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Theology","profession":"Temple Scribe","start":-500,"end":-400,"median":-450,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[35.234156,31.776679]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/a4578a12-146d-424c-9113-01a0b0bf3c0e","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Anaxagoras of Klazomenai 1","dominant_interest":"Philosophy","source_mentioned_in":"On Exile","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0480 BC","end_date":"0428 BC","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Geometry; Cosmology, Astronomy","start":-480,"end":-428,"median":-454,"eans":{"p":{"no":73}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/d8a1fb48-becd-4018-93a2-60b79f519e36","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Anaxagoras of Klazomenai 2","dominant_interest":"Philosophy","source_mentioned_in":"On Exile","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0480 BC","end_date":"0428 BC","location":"Klazomenai","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Geometry; Cosmology, Astronomy","start":-480,"end":-428,"median":-454,"eans":{"p":{"no":73}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[26.77415952,38.36467713]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/dada87ae-7529-4622-989e-c3d3bbe6b02f","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Anaxagoras of Klazomenai 3","dominant_interest":"Philosophy","source_mentioned_in":"On Exile","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0480 BC","end_date":"0428 BC","location":"Lampsakos","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Geometry; Cosmology, Astronomy","start":-480,"end":-428,"median":-454,"eans":{"p":{"no":73}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[26.68998,40.34869]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/72d9247f-5735-4f55-97b2-1f862e93e668","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Antiphon of Athens","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Physics, Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (T), Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (S)","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","proof_type":"Direct Proof","start_date":"0450 BC","end_date":"0400 BC","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Geometry","start":-450,"end":-400,"median":-425,"eans":{"p":{"no":99}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/3292cc88-44b9-4e55-be9f-ebbaa038d6cf","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Aristophanes","dominant_interest":"Play","source_mentioned_in":"_Birds_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0446 BC","end_date":"0386 BC","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Playwright","start":-446,"end":-386,"median":-416,"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/0e1d686c-069b-4ffe-85fc-baae30131423","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Hippokrates of Khios","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (T), Posterior Analytics, Sophistic Refutations","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","proof_type":"Direct Proof","start_date":"0440 BC","end_date":"0400 BC","location":"Khios","place_type":"island","interesrt":"History; Geometry","start":-440,"end":-400,"median":-420,"eans":{"p":{"no":401}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[26.053,38.414]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/5a392e6b-9737-46eb-927b-3590a4720537","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Hippokrates of Khios","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (T), Posterior Analytics, Sophistic Refutations","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","proof_type":"Direct Proof","start_date":"0440 BC","end_date":"0400 BC","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"History; Geometry","start":-440,"end":-400,"median":-420,"eans":{"p":{"no":401}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/bffd35df-9aed-4e13-a98d-cca258ad6c94","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Meton of Athens","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Birds","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0440 BC","end_date":"0410 BC","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Astronomy; Mathematics","start":-440,"end":-410,"median":-425,"eans":{"p":{"no":551}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/d15af0ae-5156-44b4-8e2a-aebb238d2ddc","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Hippias of Elis","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"On Euclid Book 1","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0440 BC","end_date":"0400 BC","location":"Eils","place_type":"settlement, theatre","interesrt":"Geometry","start":-440,"end":-400,"median":-420,"eans":{"p":{"no":400}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[21.375091,37.891781]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/61a7d4e3-5c9f-4acf-9221-f319e99c8be3","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Plato","dominant_interest":"Philosophy","source_mentioned_in":"_Repiblic_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0390 BC","end_date":"0347 BC","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy","start":-390,"end":-347,"median":-369,"eans":{"p":{"no":667}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/7b90561d-13f4-4f74-a949-dfc1abe694b0","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Bruson of Herakleia Pontike","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Aristotle's Sophistic Refutations, Posterior Analytics, Sophistic Refutations","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","proof_type":"By priciples outside geometry","start_date":"0380 BC","end_date":"0350 BC","location":"Herakleia Pontike","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Geometry; Philosophy","start":-380,"end":-350,"median":-365,"eans":{"p":{"no":199}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[31.414722,41.284722]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/148a432e-9a77-4af4-9c85-5100f2919b30","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Deinostratos of Prokonessos","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Collection","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","proof_type":"Direct Proof","start_date":"0365 BC","end_date":"0325 BC","location":"Prokonessos","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Geometry","start":-365,"end":-325,"median":-345,"eans":{"p":{"no":229}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[27.55568,40.591686]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/4276dd9e-bbcd-4f39-bfa9-a362cac7c8de","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Eudoxos of Knidos 1","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"On Euclid Book 1, Elements","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0365 AD","end_date":"0340 AD","location":"Knidos","interesrt":"Geometry; Mechanics; Arithmetic; Astronomy","start":-365,"end":-340,"median":-353,"eans":{"p":{"no":310}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[27.69261325,36.73328265]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/f9a77094-0ad9-4827-b052-40bea571e171","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Eudoxos of Knidos 2","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"On Euclid Book 1, Elements","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0365 AD","end_date":"0340 AD","location":"Athens","interesrt":"Geometry; Mechanics; Arithmetic; Astronomy","start":-365,"end":-340,"median":-353,"eans":{"p":{"no":310}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/ab5cd0f2-28f5-4ba2-9eaf-22715e03746a","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Eudoxos of Knidos 3","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"On Euclid Book 1, Elements","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0365 AD","end_date":"0340 AD","location":"Alexandria","interesrt":"Geometry; Mechanics; Arithmetic; Astronomy","start":-365,"end":-340,"median":-353,"eans":{"p":{"no":310}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.904133,31.195371]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/64212aec-7882-4558-b5b1-a562c4bd16f3","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Eudoxos of Knidos 4","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"On Euclid Book 1, Elements","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0365 AD","end_date":"0340 AD","location":"Hellespont","interesrt":"Geometry; Mechanics; Arithmetic; Astronomy","start":-365,"end":-340,"median":-353,"eans":{"p":{"no":310}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[26.4768661,40.21880802]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/57f800c2-24e3-4792-86bf-2f0ddd40a642","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Aristotle 1","dominant_interest":"Philosophy","source_mentioned_in":"_Physics_. Commentary on Aristotle's Categories","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0355 BC","end_date":"0322 BC","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Physics; Logic; Natural Science; Astronomy","profession":"Teacher","start":-355,"end":-322,"median":-339,"eans":{"p":{"no":142}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/5e02c4d0-c3f2-4994-98ef-d948058c7413","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Aristotle 2","dominant_interest":"Philosophy","source_mentioned_in":"_Physics_. Commentary on Aristotle's Categories","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0355 BC","end_date":"0322 BC","location":"Khalkis","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Physics; Logic; Natural Science; Astronomy","profession":"Teacher","start":-355,"end":-322,"median":-339,"eans":{"p":{"no":142}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.602,38.464]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/492eec7f-687f-43c2-be1b-f84537134601","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Aristotle 3","dominant_interest":"Philosophy","source_mentioned_in":"_Physics_. Commentary on Aristotle's Categories","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0355 BC","end_date":"0322 BC","location":"Mieza (Macedonia)","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Physics; Logic; Natural Science; Astronomy","profession":"Teacher","start":-355,"end":-322,"median":-339,"eans":{"p":{"no":142}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[22.122616,40.644802]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/c306863c-f7a8-4e61-b305-f0851d371121","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Eudemos of Rhodes 1","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (S)","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0330 BC","end_date":"0285 BC","location":"Rhodes","place_type":"island,settlement,temple-2,stadion","interesrt":"Philosophy; Logic; Natural Science; History; Mathematics","profession":"Teacher","start":-330,"end":-285,"median":-308,"eans":{"p":{"no":309}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[28.15629,36.41451]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/9986bf01-2bca-4b15-b4f8-8c627dd54604","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Eudemos of Rhodes 2","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (S)","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0330 BC","end_date":"0285 BC","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Logic; Natural Science; History; Mathematics","profession":"Teacher","start":-330,"end":-285,"median":-308,"eans":{"p":{"no":309}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/ed67487c-19f7-40e7-b73f-8d4cd70ad4c3","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Euclid of Alexandria","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Measurement of a Circle _Elements_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0300 BC","end_date":"0260 BC","location":"Alexandria","place_type":"cemetery,temple-2,architecturalcomplex,theatre,port,settlement","interesrt":"Mathematics; Geometry; Arithmetic; Logic","start":-300,"end":-260,"median":-280,"eans":{"p":{"no":304}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.904133,31.195371]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/9c61440e-878e-4d58-a826-538726089d22","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Archimedes of Surakousai","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"_Measurement of a Circle_, Metrica, Algamest, Commentary on Aristotle's Categories, Collection","direct_work_on_problem":"Y & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","proof_type":"Proof by Contradiction / Exhaustion","start_date":"0250 BC","end_date":"0212 BC","location":"Syracuse","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Geometry; Mechanics; Arithmetic; Astronomy","start":-250,"end":-212,"median":-231,"eans":{"p":{"no":125}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[15.29382,37.05963]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/2209a385-d070-4e34-8319-474f5e1e2cae","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Nikomedes","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Aristotle's Categories, Collection","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","proof_type":"Direct Proof","start_date":"0225 BC","end_date":"0200 BC","interesrt":"Mathematics; Geometry","start":-225,"end":-200,"median":-213,"eans":{"p":{"no":580}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":null},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/ef87837b-24aa-4470-90ee-2c999f34425c","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Apollonius of Perge","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Archimedes' Measurement of a Circle, Commentary on Aristotle's Categories","direct_work_on_problem":"Y & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"0220 BC","end_date":"0170 BC","location":"Perge","place_type":"theatre,settlement,stadion","interesrt":"Geometry","start":-220,"end":-170,"median":-195,"eans":{"p":{"no":114}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[30.854274,36.961406]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/13c27171-1881-4cef-a4e6-897042f0b233","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Karpos of Antioch","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Aristotle's Categories","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0010 BC","end_date":"0040 AD","location":"Antioch","place_type":"amphitheatre,settlement,urban","interesrt":"Mathematics; Astronomy; Mechanics","start":-10,"end":40,"median":15,"eans":{"p":{"no":468}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[36.165318,36.200663]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/45512d46-9c46-42a5-9fb0-35b8a88f4073","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Sextius, Q the Pythagorean","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Aristotle's Categories","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0005 AD","end_date":"0040 AD","location":"Rome","place_type":"settlement,urban","interesrt":"Philosophy; Science","start":5,"end":40,"median":23,"eans":{"p":{"no":738}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[12.4843457,41.89262]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/e4d566a2-5da4-4fbd-aaf8-5b05c3968f89","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Heron of Alexandria","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"_Metrica_","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"0062 AD","end_date":"0062 AD","location":"Alexandria","place_type":"cemetery,temple-2,architecturalcomplex,theatre,port,settlement","interesrt":"Astronomy; Mechanics; Geometry","start":62,"end":62,"median":62,"eans":{"p":{"no":384}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.904133,31.195371]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/7e097349-f83f-4081-ad2e-80037bf7126b","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Plutarch of Khaironeia, L. Mestrius 1","dominant_interest":"History / Biography","source_mentioned_in":"_On Exile_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0080 AD","end_date":"0120 AD","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Biography; Astronomy; Geography","profession":"Statesman","start":80,"end":120,"median":100,"eans":{"p":{"no":674}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/0e31c9a7-1b6a-4135-a6b9-8fb1530ca566","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Plutarch of Khaironeia, L. Mestrius 2","dominant_interest":"History / Biography","source_mentioned_in":"_On Exile_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0080 AD","end_date":"0120 AD","location":"Khaironeia","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Biography; Astronomy; Geography","profession":"Statesman","start":80,"end":120,"median":100,"eans":{"p":{"no":674}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[22.840365,38.493361]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/63d136c6-3221-4f1b-beb9-c4ef5fda6488","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Galen of Pergamon 1","dominant_interest":"Medicine","source_mentioned_in":"_De Animi Cuicslibet precatorium digitone et curatiore_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0115 AD","end_date":"0215 AD","location":"Pergamum","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Medicine, Philosophy","profession":"Doctor, teacher","start":115,"end":215,"median":165,"eans":{"p":{"no":335}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[27.18453033,39.13121333]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/7c2aa7d1-7fee-4ba7-9de8-75746b920cec","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Galen of Pergamon 2","dominant_interest":"Medicine","source_mentioned_in":"_De Animi Cuicslibet precatorium digitone et curatiore_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0115 AD","end_date":"0215 AD","location":"Smyrna","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Medicine, Philosophy","profession":"Doctor, teacher","start":115,"end":215,"median":165,"eans":{"p":{"no":335}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[27.141387,38.41719605]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/d7e0b982-4cd6-486b-a871-b48233c1ebb7","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Galen of Pergamon 3","dominant_interest":"Medicine","source_mentioned_in":"_De Animi Cuicslibet precatorium digitone et curatiore_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0115 AD","end_date":"0215 AD","location":"Corinth","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Medicine, Philosophy","profession":"Doctor, teacher","start":115,"end":215,"median":165,"eans":{"p":{"no":335}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[22.87923202,37.90552218]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/b778854e-8d51-4091-a5d4-374f471f6075","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Galen of Pergamon 4","dominant_interest":"Medicine","source_mentioned_in":"_De Animi Cuicslibet precatorium digitone et curatiore_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0115 AD","end_date":"0215 AD","location":"Alexandria","place_type":"cemetery,temple-2,architecturalcomplex,theatre,port,settlement","interesrt":"Medicine, Philosophy","profession":"Doctor, teacher","start":115,"end":215,"median":165,"eans":{"p":{"no":335}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.904133,31.195371]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/9b10be67-a99c-4d07-821d-e89935b239aa","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Galen of Pergamon 5","dominant_interest":"Medicine","source_mentioned_in":"_De Animi Cuicslibet precatorium digitone et curatiore_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0115 AD","end_date":"0215 AD","location":"Rome","place_type":"settlement,urban","interesrt":"Medicine, Philosophy","profession":"Doctor, teacher","start":115,"end":215,"median":165,"eans":{"p":{"no":335}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[12.4843457,41.89262]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/8d56e17c-668a-42fa-92c1-0026357678b5","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Ptolemy","dominant_interest":"Geography / Astronomy","source_mentioned_in":"_Syntaxia Mathematica_","direct_work_on_problem":"N & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"0127 AD","end_date":"0146 AD","location":"Alexandria","place_type":"cemetery,temple-2,architecturalcomplex,theatre,port,settlement","interesrt":"Mathematics; Astronomy; Cartogtraphy; Harmonics; Optics; Geography","start":127,"end":146,"median":137,"eans":{"p":{"no":706}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.904133,31.195371]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/dce07868-e20f-4b22-b2b3-fee70b185db7","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Alexander of Aphrodisias 1","dominant_interest":"Philosophical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_Commentary on Aristotle's Sophistic Refutations_, Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (S)","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0200 AD","end_date":"0200 AD","location":"Aphrodisias","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy","profession":"Teacher","start":200,"end":200,"median":200,"eans":{"p":{"no":54}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[28.723217,37.709463]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/8f2d9fd8-8ec7-459b-a4ab-199542f0ece0","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Alexander of Aphrodisias 2","dominant_interest":"Philosophical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_Commentary on Aristotle's Sophistic Refutations_, Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (S)","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0200 AD","end_date":"0200 AD","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy","profession":"Teacher","start":200,"end":200,"median":200,"eans":{"p":{"no":54}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/adc8748b-b624-42b5-bbae-c2cd4553d458","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Sporus of Nikaia","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"Collection","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","proof_type":"Proof by circluar argument","start_date":"0200 AD","end_date":"0300 AD","location":"Nikaia","place_type":"theatre,settlement","interesrt":"Geometry; Natural Science","start":200,"end":300,"median":250,"eans":{"p":{"no":753}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.715443,40.426679]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/6dd31272-5df2-48f5-a91a-ac4e8b89391a","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Pappos of Alexandria","dominant_interest":"Mathematics","source_mentioned_in":"_Collection_","direct_work_on_problem":"Y","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","proof_type":"Proof by Contradiction / Exhaustion","start_date":"0285 AD","end_date":"0320 AD","location":"Alexandria","place_type":"cemetery,temple-2,architecturalcomplex,theatre,port,settlement","interesrt":"Astronomy; Arithmetic; Geometry","start":285,"end":320,"median":303,"eans":{"p":{"no":611}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.904133,31.195371]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/cf8d5a9c-6712-4e38-8118-f84dd4e1cef3","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Iamblikhos of Khalkis (Syria)","dominant_interest":"Philosophy","source_mentioned_in":"Commentary on Aristotle's Categories","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0300 AD","end_date":"0327 AD","location":"Khlakis","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy","start":300,"end":327,"median":314,"eans":{"p":{"no":430}},"extant_source":"N"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[37.009719,36.007956]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/025fcd6a-464b-4bac-9204-239b0ede4e97","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Themistios of Buzantion","dominant_interest":"Philosophical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (T)_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0340 AD","end_date":"0385 AD","location":"Buzantion (Constantinople)","place_type":"settlement,urban","interesrt":"Philosophy; Natural Science","start":340,"end":385,"median":363,"eans":{"p":{"no":783}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[28.975926,41.012379]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/6cf90ce3-ca00-44b7-b216-f3aaa483bea4","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Proklos of Lukia 1","dominant_interest":"Mathematical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_On Euclid Book 1_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0430 AD","end_date":"0485 AD","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Natural Science; Cosmology; Mathematics","profession":"Teacher","start":430,"end":485,"median":458,"eans":{"p":{"no":698}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/fdd8ba0c-dcbd-40ba-83ff-9e2b6ff7e0fc","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Proklos of Lukia 2","dominant_interest":"Mathematical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_On Euclid Book 1_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0430 AD","end_date":"0486 AD","location":"Buzantion (Constantinople)","place_type":"settlement,urban","interesrt":"Philosophy; Natural Science; Cosmology; Mathematics","profession":"Teacher","start":430,"end":485,"median":458,"eans":{"p":{"no":698}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[28.975926,41.012379]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/35fc4b40-59c3-4f4a-8f37-9c6740b6edca","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Proklos of Lukia 3","dominant_interest":"Mathematical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_On Euclid Book 1_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0430 AD","end_date":"0488 AD","location":"Xanthos","place_type":"theatre,settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Natural Science; Cosmology; Mathematics","profession":"Teacher","start":430,"end":485,"median":458,"eans":{"p":{"no":698}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.31836,36.355934]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/2a86eb33-7942-4474-8477-33b3449316bd","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Proklos of Lukia 4","dominant_interest":"Mathematical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_On Euclid Book 1_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0430 AD","end_date":"0489 AD","location":"Lydia","place_type":"cemetery,temple-2,architecturalcomplex,theatre,port,settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Natural Science; Cosmology; Mathematics","profession":"Teacher","start":430,"end":485,"median":458,"eans":{"p":{"no":698}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.904133,31.195371]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/29a46c6f-16d0-45b2-a76b-faeb3e936754","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Marinos of Neapolis 1","dominant_interest":"Mathematical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_Commentary on Euclid's Data_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0460 AD","end_date":"0495 AD","location":"Neapolis","place_type":"settlement,amphitheatre,amphitheater","interesrt":"Philosophy, Mathematics","profession":"Teacher","start":450,"end":495,"median":473,"eans":{"p":{"no":532}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[35.262911,32.218685]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/4ee85edb-1775-4bba-b834-3739327006d0","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Marinos of Neapolis 2","dominant_interest":"Mathematical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_Commentary on Euclid's Data_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0460 AD","end_date":"0495 AD","location":"Athens","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy, Mathematics","profession":"Teacher","start":450,"end":495,"median":473,"eans":{"p":{"no":532}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[23.726464,37.971687]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/5809590f-613f-48c8-961f-4fd886bf5bc7","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Eutokios of Askalon","dominant_interest":"Mathematical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_Commentary on Archimedes' Measurement of a Circle_","direct_work_on_problem":"Y & PI","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"Y","start_date":"0510 AD","end_date":"0530 AD","location":"Askalon","place_type":"settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Mathematics; Geometry","start":510,"end":530,"median":520,"eans":{"p":{"no":324}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[34.54732,31.66426]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/ae6e17c5-1db0-4d1d-9536-aed99d2895b0","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Joannes Philoponis","dominant_interest":"Philosophical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_Commentary on Aristotle's Prior Analytics_, _Commentary on Aristotle's Posterior Analytics_,_Commentary on Aristotle's Physics_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0510 AD","end_date":"0570 AD","location":"Alexandria","place_type":"cemetery,temple-2,architecturalcomplex,theatre,port,settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy, Mathematics","start":510,"end":570,"median":540,"eans":{"p":{"no":436}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.904133,31.195371]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/79f402d4-4dc0-48ee-925f-cdb812f78f3a","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Simplicius of Kilikia 1","dominant_interest":"Philosophical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (S)_, _Commentary on Aristotle's Categories_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0530 AD","end_date":"0538 AD","location":"Alexandria","place_type":"cemetery,temple-2,architecturalcomplex,theatre,port,settlement","interesrt":"Philosophy; Cosmology; Physics","start":530,"end":538,"median":534,"eans":{"p":{"no":743}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[29.904133,31.195371]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/fc61ab35-d05a-4cae-8e0e-6be5c4515346","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"Simplicius of Kilikia 2","dominant_interest":"Philosophical Commentary","source_mentioned_in":"_Commentary on Aristotle's Physics (S)_, _Commentary on Aristotle's Categories_","direct_work_on_problem":"N","type_(o_p,_hc,_pi)":{},"approximation_of_pi":"N","start_date":"0530 AD","end_date":"0538 AD","location":"Kilikia","place_type":"region","interesrt":"Philosophy; Cosmology; Physics","start":530,"end":538,"median":534,"eans":{"p":{"no":743}},"extant_source":"Y"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[33.25,36.25]}},{"@id":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes/92ed8bd3-4aee-45c8-b83c-c8ac2cdb3ee6","type":"Feature","properties":{"title":"FILL"},"geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[20,40]}}],"indexing":{"@type":"Dataset","name":"Quadrature of the Circle Nodes with Locations split nodes","description":"","license":"https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/","identifier":"https://w3id.org/Quadrature%20of%20the%20Circle%20Nodes%20with%20Locations%20split%20nodes","temporalCoverage":"1066/2022","spatialCoverage":{"@type":"GeoShape","box":"0.580101 0.00149 60.355 9.78667","geo":{"@type":"GeoShape","box":"29.3149635 12.4843457 41.89262 48.2537285"}}}}